<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="aa_promises_lit">If we are painstaking about this phase of our development, we will be 
        amazed before we are half way through. We are going to know a new freedom and a new happiness. 
        We will not regret the past nor wish to shut the door on it. We will comprehend the word serenity 
        and we will know peace. No matter how far down the scale we have gone, we will see how our experience 
        can benefit others. That feeling of uselessness and selfpity will disappear. We will lose interest in 
        selfish things and gain interest in our fellows. Self-seeking will slip away. Our whole attitude and 
        outlook upon life will change. Fear of people and of economic insecurity will leave us. We will 
        intuitively know how to handle situations which used to baffle us. We will suddenly realize that God is 
        doing for us what we could not do for ourselves.\n\nAre these extravagant promises? We think not. They 
        are being fulfilled among us—sometimes quickly, sometimes slowly. They will always materialize if we 
        work for them.\n</string>
		
	<string name="aa_how_it_works_lit">Rarely have we seen a person fail who has thoroughly followed our path. 
	    Those who do not recover are people who cannot or will not completely give themselves to this simple 
	    program, usually men and women who are constitutionally incapable of being honest with themselves. There 
	    are such unfortunates. They are not at fault; they seem to have been born that way. They are naturally 
	    incapable of grasping and developing a manner of living which demands rigorous honesty. Their chances 
	    are less than average. There are those, too, who suffer from grave emotional and mental disorders, but 
	    many of them do recover if they have the capacity to be honest. Our stories disclose in a general way 
	    what we used to be like, what happened, and what we are like now. If you have decided you want what we 
	    have and are willing to go to any length to get it &#8212; then you are ready to take certain steps.
	    \n\n1. We admitted we were powerless over alcohol—that our lives had become unmanageable.\n\n2. Came to 
	    believe that a power greater than ourselves could restore us to sanity.\n\n3. Made a decision to turn 
	    our will and our lives over to the care of God as we understood Him.\n\n4. Made a searching and fearless 
	    moral inventory of ourselves.\n\n5. Admitted to God, to ourselves, and to another human being the exact
	    nature of our wrongs.\n\n6. Were entirely ready to have God remove all these defects of character.\n\n7.
	    Humbly asked Him to remove our shortcomings.\n\n8. Made a list of all persons we had harmed, and became 
	    willing to make amends to them all.\n\n9. Made direct amends to such people wherever possible, except 
	    when to do so would injure them or others.\n\n10. Continued to take personal inventory, and when we were 
	    wrong, promptly admitted it.\n\n11. Sought through prayer and meditation to improve our conscious contact
	    with God as we understood Him, praying only for knowledge of His will for us and the power to carry that 
	    out.\n\n12. Having had a spiritual awakening as the result of these steps, we tried to carry this 
	    message to alcoholics, and to practice these principles in all our affairs.\n</string>
	    
	<string name="aa_twelve_traditions_lit">1. Our common welfare should come first; personal recovery depends 
	    upon A.A. unity.\n\n2. For our group purpose there is but one ultimate authority—a loving God as He may 
	    express Himself in our group conscience. Our leaders are but trusted servants; they do not govern.\n\n3.
	    The only requirement for A.A. membership is a desire to stop drinking.\n\n4. Each group should be 
	    autonomous except in matters affecting other groups or A.A. as a whole.\n\n5. Each group has but one 
	    primary purpose—to carry its message to the alcoholic who still suffers.\n\n6. An A.A. group ought never
	    endorse, finance, or lend the A.A. name to any related facility or outside enterprise, lest problems of 
	    money, property, and prestige divert us from our primary purpose.\n\n7. Every A.A. group ought to be 
	    fully self-supporting, declining outside contributions.\n\n8. Alcoholics Anonymous should remain forever 
	    non-professional, but our service centers may employ special workers.\n\n9. A.A., as such, ought never 
	    be organized; but we may create service boards or committees directly responsible to those they serve.
	    \n\n10. Alcoholics Anonymous has no opinion on outside issues; hence the A.A. name ought never be drawn 
	    into public controversy.\n\n11. Our public relations policy is based on attraction rather than promotion;
	    we need always maintain personal anonymity at the level of press, radio, and films.\n\n12. Anonymity is 
	    the spiritual foundation of all our traditions, ever reminding us to place principles before 
	    personalities.\n</string>
		
	<string name="aa_preamble_lit">Alcoholics Anonymous is a fellowship of men and women who share their 
	    experience, strength and hope with each other that they may solve their common problem and help others 
	    to recover from alcoholism. The only requirement for membership is a desire to stop drinking. There are 
	    no dues or fees for AA membership; we are self-supporting through our own contributions. AA is not 
	    allied with any sect, denomination, politics, organization or institution; does not wish to engage in 
	    any controversy; neither endorses nor opposes any causes. Our primary purpose is to stay sober and help 
	    other alcoholics to achieve sobriety.\n</string>
	    
	<string name="serenity_prayer_lit">God\nGrant me the serenity,\nTo accept the things I cannot change,\nThe courage
	    to change the things I can,\nAnd the wisdom to know the difference</string>
</resources>
